<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<resources>

    <string name="help_wallet">
        <![CDATA[
        <p>
            The upper left part of the screen displays your balance in Peercoins and one selected national currency.
            Tap to go to the list of national currencies, and tap on one of the currencies to select it as default.
        </p>
        <p>
            The QR code on the right contains your peercoin address and can be used for scanning by another party.
            Tap on the QR code to get a larger version of it.
        </p>
        <p>
            The bottom of the screen is covered by your transactions list, which is empty at the beginning.
            Pending transactions are greyed out until they are confirmed.
            Tap on one entry to add the senders or receivers address to the address book.
            Swipe left or right to apply filters to the list.
        </p>
        <p>
            You can send or request coins by tapping the buttons in the action bar.
            More options are available in the options menu.
        </p>
        ]]>
    </string>
    <string name="help_request_coins">
        <![CDATA[
        <p>
            Using this dialog, you can request coins from another person (who should already have installed Peercoin Wallet).
        </p>
        <p>
            First, you can enter an amount of Peercoins to request.
        </p>
        <p>
            Then, you either have the generated QR code scanned by the other person.
            Or, you can send your request to a remote person with the share button in the action bar.
            The other person will have to click the Peercoin URL.
        </p>
        <p>
            Either way, the other person will be presented a dialog for sending coins with all fields pre-populated.
            If she accepts, all she needs to do is sending the payment.
        </p>
        ]]>
    </string>
    <string name="help_send_coins">
        <![CDATA[
        <p>
            You have initiated the process of sending coins.
            You came here either through the main screen or by clicking on a payment URI in your mobile browser.
        </p>
        <p>
            First, you specify the Peercoin or supported ShapeShift coin address to pay to.
            The address will autocomplete from known entries in your address book.
            You can also scan QR codes with addresses or requests by pressing the QR button in the action bar.
        </p>
        <p>
            You can specify a destination coin from the dropdown menu. You can specify the amount in Peercoin or your 
            local currency. If the coin is not Peercoin, the transfer will be made using ShapeShift. For ShapeShift coins 
            the rate and foreign amount will be estimated unless you specify an exact foreign amount.
        </p>
        <p>
            You can enter a payment while being offline.
            It will be sent on next restart of Peercoin Wallet.
            If you want a payment to be processed as fast as possible, make sure you are well connected (i.e. on a WLAN).
        </p>
        <p>
            Note:
            Payments are irreversible!
            Always check the receiving address.
            The third-party ShapeShift API is used to send to coins other than Peercoin. There is no guarentee that ShapeShift 
            will function correctly, or at all.
        </p>
        ]]>
    </string>
    <string name="help_safety">
        <![CDATA[
        <p>
            <b>Important safety notes:</b>
        </p>
        <p>
            Peercoins are stored on the device.
            <b>If you lose it, you\'ll lose your Peercoins.</b>
        </p>
        <p>
            This means you need to <b>back up your wallet</b>!
            Use the in-app backup facility for this, rather than a third party backup app.
            Keep your backup safe and remember the password.
        </p>
        <p>
            <b>Before uninstalling</b> (or clearing app data/wiping your device), <b>transfer your Peercoins to another wallet</b>.
            Remaining Peercoins will be lost.
        </p>
        <p>
            <b>Payments are irreversible</b>.
            If you send your Peercoins into the void, there is almost no way to get them back.
        </p>
        <p>
            <b>Keep your mobile device safe!</b>
            Do not root your device.
            Do only install apps you fully trust.
            Malicious apps could be trying to steal your wallet.
        </p>
        <p>
            Keep the risk low!
            <b>Only use with small amounts</b> for day use.
        </p>
        ]]>
    </string>
    <string name="help_trusted_servers">
        <![CDATA[
        <p>
            Here is a list of trusted servers that obtain block hashes for blockchain validation. These servers will 
            never have access to your funds, but dishonest servers may trick your wallet onto an incorrect blockchain.
        </p>
        <p>
            Servers are listed in order of priority, with high priority coming first. Priority numbers are shown on the 
            left. You may reorder servers by draging the slider handles on the left.
        </p>
        <p>
            Servers with the highest priority will be tried first, in a random order. If all of the highest priority 
            servers have failed, the servers with the next priority will be attempted and so on.
        </p>
        <p>
            The last successful server is highlighted in bold. Green servers have been successfully tried. Red servers 
            have failed on the last attempt. Grey servers have not been tried. Beware that green servers may still give 
            bad block hashes.
        </p>
        <p>
            You may add new servers or edit existing ones. Clicking on a server will you give options to edit or delete a 
            server. You must provide a server name and valid URL for the server. You may also select an option for the 
            server to have equal priority to the server above it.
        </p>
        <p>
            Server URLs should implement the getvalidhashes API. If you need to restore the default settings, you may do 
            so in the menu.
        </p>
        ]]>
    </string>

</resources>
